Today is my XXIO driver's debut on the course.
This is the first time I've taken her out today.
Unveiling!
Wow!
Oh!
Hey, don't go, don't go, don't go.
Hello.
The Sunshine Girls.
This is the golf ladies from Hyuga.
Today we're visiting the Tamagawa Golf Club.
It's a river here.
Can you see it's a river?
It's a river.
It's a river!
Next to the river.
The river is flowing.
So, today's your first day on the course.
How do you like it?
I'm happy.
I'm very happy.
It's your first time, right?
I've never been here before.
It's my first time.
But, you know, in the comments on YouTube.
You've been to the course before, right?
It's my very first time.
I saved it for today.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I thought, "Well, if I'm going to go to all this trouble, I might as well do it on YouTube.
I'm here.
hmm?
We went shopping last time.
We went shopping last time... at the Dollar Five... so it's time to show you what we got.
Here's the top I bought, please.
cute, scary, I want to show you something, I want to show you something forward
Okay, here we go. Yay.
Yay, cute, nice, con... con golf wear, socks in con, socks in con.
Con socks. Con shoes.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la.
Yes. And Kumi, your golf outfit, too?
So cute! I'm wearing this light blue one.
They look great on you. So cute!
White high socks.
I bought these before.
The golf shoes are a little purple.
Different color!
I said that in front of you.
Actually, it's a different color.
She said, "This looks like Azaka's outfit.
Really?
It's like playing golf in the sun.
I was caught in the act.
I'd get in trouble if I danced here.
That's it.
I'm sorry. You're cute.
What do you think I am?
What do you think it is?
Moon, star.
What was that dance again?
The moon and the stars.
Everyone dancing
Constellation Pose
We are
The moon and the stars
Aza towa
The two of us.
But it's a little cold. It's so cold today.
We're wearing the same brand of jackets.
And while wearing it, we'll do karaoke.
Yes, this is how we'll play golf.
May I wear it? It's cold.
Let's put it on. Let's put it on.
It's so cold.
It's really cold today. About four times colder than you'd imagine.
It's by the river.
I couldn't catch it.
My hands were cold.
My hands are cold.
I may have been a little tongue-tied today, but...
Yes, we have a lisp today
Forgive us.
I didn't get a chance to check.
In this state...
I'd like to introduce you to our clubs.
This is our golf bag.
Why don't you start with Aya's?
I'll do it first.
My golf bag.
This is my golf bag. I chose the Onof golf bag.
It's cute. It's very Urbile.
Here's what I bought in my Onof golf bag.
I love this one.
Oh, yeah?
It's a ZEXIO driver.
Cute. White.
Yeah, white.
White.
White is really cute.
It's so pretty.
Here's the water.
It's so cute. It's my favorite.
I love it. And the utilities.
I bought the same ones for the utility and the iron set.
These are for Jexie, too.
They're pink.
What's this?
What are these?
I thought they were jammed.
Yes, they're stuck.
These are the irons for Jexie.
You bought them as a set, right?
Yes, I bought them in Punpink.
Here's the pattern.
Rock, paper, scissors!
I changed the kitty pattern to a kitty pattern to a kitty pattern... it's a high-end pattern, so yes, I did my best to make it look good.
I'm going to do my best to use this pattern to demonstrate my wonderful enthusiasm.
I'll do my best to demonstrate the power of this pattern to you.
I'd like to do my best so that I can use this pattern to demonstrate my wonderful enthusiasm I'd like to do my best so that I can use this high-end pattern to demonstrate my wonderful enthusiasm
I'm going to try my best to use this pattern to show off my wonderful enthusiasm.
I'm not sure what to say, but I'm sure you'll be able to find a good deal of information on this site.
I'm actually buying a new year's gift for myself too!
I bought a set of Zexia red irons.
I bought a set of red Zexia irons... matching ours.
The hardness of the shaft is different between Kumi's and mine.
The hardness of the shaft is a little different... but Mr. Sasaki taught me how to use them.
I'm a little stronger now. My favorite is this one. Isn't she cute?
This is from New Era, and it's my favorite driver cover
It's cute. I've had this for a while. It's a putter.
Putter is important. It's the most important thing.
Ta-da!
Cat!
A devil cat!
They're the same!
I'm very enthusiastic about this putter.
It's meaningless if I don't let her show off her abilities.
I'll do my best to make her look like the right woman!
There's no similarity.
You're saying.
Let's do our best.
Déjà vu.
Together.
We're the same.
Yes, we are.
Let's go for it.
That's what it looked like.
Shall we get on with it?
Let's do it.
Let's do it!
Let's get out on the course!
Let's go!
Let's put on our Hamakawa Golf Club caps!
Yeah!
Good luck, Kubi! Let's start with a swing.
Here we go! Off you go! I'm off!
Wow!
There it is!
Crunch! But it flew! It was beautiful!
For a first time, I'd say that's pretty good. I'll take that as a compliment.
Okay, let's go for it. Let's go for it. I'm nervous.
As usual.
It's all right, it's all right. Nervousness.
You flew straight. You flew straight.
That's good. Shall we go look for the ball? Let's go find the ball.
Maybe I'm not flying as fast as you, so you'll have to hit it from me. Is that right?
Yes, you hit it from the person farthest away. I see.
We are both making our debut with the hose, and my dad loves gold. That's right.
My dad loves it. My dad. Dad.
He taught us.
What you should never do is
To get in front of the person you're hitting.
Really?
There's Qui's ball!
There it is!
I found the ball.
I found it!
Kui's ball.
It hit this tree.
It's bulky.
I have about 80 yards to go!
So, I was using a 7-iron earlier.
I'm going to use about a 9-iron.
Yes, I think so.
I'd like to shoot it.
That's a good choice.
Yes, thank you.
One choice.
Like this, right?
Oh, no, that's hard.
Go for it!
Straight!
It's getting closer.
Closer!
Okay, next, let's go find Aya's ball.
There you are!
Oh, my goodness.
There it is!
That's 60, so...
I should've done it with a 9 or something.
I think I can do it.
Do you want to try 9? Okay, then.
Let's try 9.
It's kind of backwards, isn't it?
Yeah, that's something you don't get to do on the practice range.
I've never done that before.
Any jams?
No, I'm not.
I'll use it.
No, really, don't.
Oh, my God, the grass is resisting.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I got it.
I can feel it.
Yeah, I got it.
The grass is really grassy. Shiba?
There's so much I didn't know about the big world.
There's so much I didn't know.
Straight up, straight up.
This is what it means to be an instructor.
Next three strokes.
Oh, no.
Why? - It's okay.
It's okay, forget about it.
Thank you for your help.
Oh! Nice shot!
Did I fly too far?
Did I go a little too far?
It went too far.
But I hit it really well.
I wish I could have hit that here.
That's golf.
It was a really good hit.
I hit it really well.
It's just, you know, the distance.
It's all about the distance.
It's a difficult course, isn't it?
It's not all about the distance.
It's not.
It's like 20 yards from here.
You practiced, right?
You practiced.
I practiced my approach.
You can do it.
Then it's 3, right? Tomi-chan.
Four?
We're just starting.
Pearl, you wanna go for it? Twenty yards, right? I went a little too far earlier.
A little bit, but the green's this way. Yeah, I'm gonna hit it a little bit to the right.
Whoa!
That's so good! How's that? I went too far! It's rolling! But did I get in?
It's so good!
It's going! You had good aim! But it just rolled away a little bit! It rolls! That was so good! That was great! Now that's a pair! It's good, isn't it?
How far did you get? My ball! Let's find it! You're flying too high! Oh! It's gone! Lost boy!
Your stray! You go that way! Isn't this really hard? Looks so hard! Oh, my gosh! The slope!
I can't see the green! You can't see it! It's 30 yards! That's 30 yards, so that's the approach we just did!
You mean uphill, right? Do you think you can make it? I can do it!
Oh! Over! Over! How's it look? We're going over!
Oh, almost there! Almost green! Almost green!
Aya just barely missed the green! Almost there, really!
So I'm in a pattern from here!
And I'm farther away, so Kumi-chan... Yes, and I'm also on the green, so here comes Mark, the Mark of my dreams!
I'll stick it behind this one. Okay.
How's the bow?
It's kind of sloping, so if you hit it normally, it probably won't go straight
It's kind of downhill. It's kind of downhill.
Left center of gravity. Left center of gravity.
Aya, left center of gravity.
It's hard.
I can do it.
Let's do it.
Bye, Aya!
Have fun.
But, but...
That was a little too good. Because this place doesn't roll. It's not so easy.
Okay, Kumi-chan. Don't you want to mark? My mark time.
It's your mark time. My first mark time.
Here?
Oh, my God.
How was it? My first mark. I was nervous. It was my first time.
I think I made him feel good. I think Green was happy.
He tried to meet me. Okay, let's follow Kumichan's pattern.
Oh, what?
I want it. I want it so bad.
I'm glad to hear it.
Actually, Aya, it's me. How are you feeling?
How're you feeling now? Well, seeing Kumi's work was a great reference for me.
Really? You want to put it in here?
You should put it in here.
I'm in trouble.
I really want to do it.
I really want to.
Oh, that's too close.
You went a little to the right, didn't you?
I'll be in trouble if I can't get it in here.
I'll try.
Try it.
It's going in.
It's a little tough not to go in here.
Oh, it's so frustrating.
It's frustrating.
I'll let you in now.
Okay, let me in.
Oh, I'm in.
It's in. It's in. It's a long way in.
I gotta get the ball. Excuse me.
Excuse me. I'd like to go in. What's your cue? Next five.
Five's no good. Great, if it goes in here, it's going in, definitely a double bogey.
Have a good day.
Oh, wow!
It's in!
Yay!
It's in, Kumi.
Hole 2, 136 yards.
Yes!
Wow!
Scary!
I'm scared! It's not in!
Thank God!
Just in time!
It stopped just in front of the bunker.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
I guess I was right on target.
Then, me...
Ai-chan, please go!
I'm scared!
I'm scared.
The whole time?
She says she's scared.
She says she's scared only when we talk about stairs.
I'm scared.
He's trying to make me less scary.
I'm sorry. But soon, soon, soon...
I'm so mad at myself, I'm thinking to myself, "What am I doing?
I heard bunkers suck you in, right?
I'm going to hit the 9 on the 9, I'm going to hit the 9 on the 9, I'm going to hit the 9 on the 9, I'm going to hit the 9 on the 9.
I'm not like this...
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm scared.
It's okay.
It's an approach. An approach.
Let's go with "p". Let's go with "p".
It's farther than practice, so go for it!
I'm going all out! I'm flying too high!
I'm going all out, aren't I?
I want to match it to something.
There it goes. A little to the left.
That's better than going into the backer.
So, you've come this far in one try, Kumiko?
That's amazing!
But the backer looks like it's going to eat me.
The backer looks like it's going to eat me.
Like a mouth... and the green one looks like an eye.
It looks like a mouth. Like a mouth. Scary.
Well, I'll hit it.
Have a good day.
I'm off.
Oh! Nice!
It's good, right?
It's so good!
All right!
I got it!
Kue, can we go to 3 houses?
Can we do 3 houses?
Fifteen yards.
Yeah, 15 yards.
That's good, right?
That's good!
You're on the green.
You're on it, right?
I'm on it. I'm on it.
It's uphill.
Straight up.
If you can go straight.
With the right amount of force.
You can do it, right?
If you can go, I believe you can get in.
I'm reading.
I'm reading the course.
A little to the right.
But the strength was good.
It went a little to the right.
That was close.
Was it a little too hard?
It's going to go in.
If I put it in, it's a par.
That's right, it's a par.
That's great.
Okay, I'm going.
Have a good day.
Ahhh...
Ohhh...
I'm sorry.
Then make it alcohol.
What do you think?
Is this going in?
Oh! It's in!
Congratulations! Bogey!
I can't tell you how many times I've done that. Next is my seventh shot.
Lucky seven! I wish I could get in.
Is it in?
It's in.
It's in. It's in. It's in.
Oh, my God.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
I don't know why it didn't hit me like that.
It didn't hit at all.
That was a little weak.
Ah! I got it. I got it.
It was a little strong.
But you rolled.
Rolled over.
That's good, right?
It's okay.
That's a little too much, don't go, don't go, don't go, don't go.
Don't go.
After you.
Nice.
Weak.
From the absolute first time is the battle of Antigone ...
Hear me, macht weiterhin.
Yes, so you made your debut on the course.
How was it?
It was quite difficult.
It was quite different from the practice.
It was totally different.
I mean, we were practicing
7-iron and driver.
I mean, we were practicing a lot.
But when we got out on the course, we only did it once.
Just the first shot.
Approaches.
Patterns.
I've realized how important it is.
I've heard it's important.
I'm not sure how important it is.
It's important...
But I realized how important it is.
I want to practice more and get better.
I want to get better.
But it was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun.
It was really fun.
It was fun. It was fun. So I want you two to practice a lot more, get better, and then we'll go to the course.
I'd like to make my real debut on the course next time.
I hope you'll continue to watch over us... with warm eyes, please.
I'd appreciate it if you could give me some advice.
Please subscribe to my channel, give me ratings and comments.
Thank you very much!